citroen.co.uk 2016-12-28

# Online Privacy Policy - Citroën United Kingdom

**DATA PROTECTION - YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We are committed to handling your personal information responsibly and protecting your privacy.For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 the data controller is Citroën UK Limited.

**What information will we collect from you?**

In order to access certain functions on our website you may be required to input some items of personal information that may include: name, address, telephone number, email address, car registration number and other contact information.  We may collect and process any personal information that you voluntarily provide to us in this way, but we will only do so in accordance with this Privacy Policy.In addition, whenever you visit our website (or any mobile version of our website), our web server automatically records analytical data about your usage.  This data is anonymous and does not identify you as an individual.  For more information about this please refer to our [Cookies Policy](http://www.citroen.co.uk/cookies).

**Where will we store your personal information?**

Please be aware that the transmission via the internet is not completely secure.  Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of the personal information transmitted to our website and any transmission is at your own risk.  However, once your personal information has been received by us, it will be stored on our secure company server and we will take all reasonable measures to keep it secure and prevent unauthorised access to it. Your personal information may be shared with third parties as set out below and also be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area, but we will always do our best to ensure that it is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**PRIVACY - OUR PLEDGE**

**What will we do with your personal information?**

We may use the personal information you provide to us for marketing research (including participating in surveys), product analysis and development, sales tracking, or to contact you for marketing or promotional purposes. We may contact you through various media including by telephone, post, SMS or email.We may share your personal information with other entities within our international group of companies ("Our Group"), with companies providing a service to us or Our Group including agents and subcontractors, or with our dealers. They will only use it for the purposes and using the contact methods set out above.If you no longer wish us to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy then you may opt out at any time by contacting us at the address directly below.

**Telephone call recording**

Telephone calls to and from Citroën, DS and our Dealers may be recorded and monitored for security purposes and to assist with staff training, under our quality control procedures.

**QUESTIONS?**

Any questions, comments or requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be redirected to Citroën Contact Centre, Citroën UK Limited, Pinley House, 2 Sunbeam Way, Coventry CV3 1ND, [CUK_ContactCentre@citroen.com](mailto:CUK_ContactCentre@citroen.com) or 0844 463 3500.
